Ashley Kelk

Mobile Number: 07476589567 Email: Ash-k-2014@hotmail.com

Profile

I am an enthusiastic, reliable, and outgoing individual who always works hard to achieve my potential. I am confident with great communication skills which allow me to work alone using my initiative but equally as well within a team. I pride myself on my high standard of time keeping and punctuality. I am a motivated individual willing to work flexible hours including weekends and bank holidays. I enjoy taking on new challenges and seeing them through to completion, while remaining compassionate and good-humoured whilst under pressure. I possess the ability to lead a team but would describe myself as a keen learner. I have the necessary experience completing and implementing important risk assessment tools vital to protecting all employees. Throughout my previous employment I have been assessed and accustomed to the policies and procedures compliant with the Health and Safety Act 1974 and Control of Substances Hazardous to Health.

Key Competencies

Teamwork Responsible

Organisation Leadership/

Management

Communication

Problem solving

Results Orientated

Computer Literate

Highly Analytical

Decision Making

Key Qualifications

- Cargo Handling in Ports Certificate.
- National Safety Passport.
- CSCS Card Construction Site Operative.
- Confined Space Certificate.
- Asbestos Awareness certificate.
- Loading Shovel. Using all attachments
- Level 1 Water Jetting Card and Part 2 Practical and Preparation.
- B1 B2 forklift licence.
- Bobcat skid steer licence.
- Managing safely certificate.
- Slingers and banksman certificate.
- Emergency first aid
- IHOSH managing safely certificate.

- Sia door Supervisor Badge
- GWO Manual Handling
- GWO Working at Heights
- GWO Enhanced First Aid
- GWO Advanced Rescue Training
- GWO Fire Awareness Training
- GWO Sea Survival Training
- GWO Basic Training in Mechanical, Electrical, Bolt tightening and Hydraulics

Experience

01-01-2023 - Present - ASSOCIATED BRITISH PORTS / (Marine Operative)

General Mooring duties of vessels on the lock & around the docks / river at Immingham

- Using VHF radio to liaise with vessels & ABP Marine staff
- Supplying vessels with fresh water
- Using hydraulic/various machinery to operate lock gates/sluices/winches
- Handling mooring boats, under supervision.
- Placing of Pneumatic fenders, in the enclosed dock and out on a tidal river at the IOH
- Removing flotsam in dock, various cleaning & painting duties
- Receiving instructions from my supervisor for Gritting in Icey conditions and implementing them, ensuring all staff and stakeholders/ships crew are safe from slips/trips and falls

Synthomer – 07-01-2022 – 30-12-2022 Support process operator

- Accurate and safe loading of bulk product to road barrels.
- Awareness and conformance of site SHE standards.
- Use of Sap systems, working with pressurised vessels and equipment.
- Following site standards such as washout and biocidal treatment of equipment.

January 2021-2022.Briggs's marine- Mooring Assistant /terminal operator.

- Mooring and unmooring vessels from 5000 tons to 115000.
- Using messenger and capstans.
- Connecting and discounting cargo hoses, and being a berth standby man to oversee vessels through load or discharge.
- Duties when on berth standby include monitoring of all moorings throughout the duration of its stay making sure the vessel stays in position throughout load or discharge.
- Repetitive hourly checks of gangway and pressure gauges and temperature of cargo.

SIA-Door supervisor

Working as a team on nightclubs having a duty of care to members of the public and bar staff.

•

<u>December 2018 to current, Port Operative – Associated British Ports</u>

Loading bag wagons with B2 forklift, also discharging bag boats, and building stacks into sheds. Drive loading shovel loading out to bulk wagons also pushing up cargo in sheds using all attachments. Also drive bobcat (skid steer) cleaning up on site and preparing sheds are clean for when vessels discharge. Also, a safety representative for my terminal, doing regular checks and site walk around with compliance team looking for improvements and always trying to improve on safety.

- Shovel Driving
- General Stevedoring
- Stevedoring Cape Vessels
- Based all over Immingham port
- Tug Driving (landside)
- Hopper Driving
- Forklift Truck

November 2016 - May 2017, High Pressure Jet Washing - Cristal Pigment UK Limited

Operating high-pressure cleaning equipment and using other cleaning materials and chemicals to achieve desired results of cleaning and sanitation.

- Brickwork Jet washing, Pavement, Render, Chewing Gum Removal.
- Graffiti Removal, Moss Algae, Lichen & Weed Removal.
- Stone Jet Washing, Carpark, Cladding & Façade Jet Washing.
- Using the pressure washer to get out tough stains and dirt.
- Properly dispose of/remove wastewater and barricade necessary drains ensuring that all work performed is EPA compliant

Industry cleaner under general supervision, operating high-pressure cleaning equipment and using other cleaning materials and chemicals to achieve desired results of cleaning and sanitation.

- Ensuring procedural documentation satisfied complete compliance with regulations and project specifications.
- Worked as part of asbestos removal team.
- Worked with a process operator carrying out duties and looking to widen my view and get better knowledge on how the plant works.
- Properly dispose of/remove wastewater and barricade necessary drains ensuring that all work performed is EPA compliant

October 2014 - August 2015, North East Lincolnshire Council

Recycling operative consisted of working efficiently as part of a team to ensure rubbish disposal was compliant to specific guidelines and regulations.

- Helping to formulate efficient and effective waste disposal plans.
- Liaising with private waste collection companies.
- Devising and administering waste management budgets.
- Managing outside contractors.
- Keeping statistical records and preparing reports.
- Ensuring compliance with current waste disposal/handling/transportation legislation.
- Monitoring levels of pollution from waste disposal sites.
- Working closely with recycling officers.
- Handling queries or complaints from the public.

Education

2002-2007- Wintringham School, Grimsby – Studied and passed GCSE courses: English, Maths & Double Science.

I hold a clean UK driving licence.

References are available on request